<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Chen Jianfeng]]></title>
  <link href="http://Ginfung.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://Ginfung.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2013-12-06T16:56:16+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://Ginfung.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[ChenJianfeng]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Homepage Chenjianfeng]]></title>
    <link href="http://Ginfung.github.io/blog/2013/10/12/this-is-my-first-article/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-12T23:22:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://Ginfung.github.io/blog/2013/10/12/this-is-my-first-article</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>[This website is under construction. Information may be not complete. Sorry for that and thanks for your understanding.]</p>

<p><img src="http://chenjianfeng.net/images/chenjf.jpg" style="float: left; margin: 0 20px 20px 0; width:120px;"/></p>

<p><strong>Correspondence:</strong> <a href="http://www.sc.sdu.edu.cn/eweb/index.htm" title="Software college">Software College</a>, <a href="http://en.sdu.edu.cn/" title="Shandong University">Shandong University</a><br />
No.1500, Shunhua Rd., Jinan City<br />
Shandong Province, P.R.C<br />
<strong>Zipcode:</strong> 250101<br />
<strong>E-mail:</strong> ginfungchan AT gmail.com or cjfameritop AT gmail.com<br />
<strong>URL:</strong> www.chenjianfeng.net</p>

<blockquote><p><a href="#about_me">About Me</a> &nbsp; <a href="#research_interest">Research Interest</a> &nbsp; <a href="#education">Education</a> &nbsp; <a href="#project">Project List</a></p></blockquote>

<h2 id="about_me">ABOUT ME</h2>


<p>I am a senior student at the software college in Shandong University,China, majoring in software engineering. Now I am applying for the graduate program for further study in the area of computer science.</p>

<h2 id="research_interest">RESEARCH INTEREST</h2>


<ul>
<li><strong>Computer Aided Geometric Design:</strong> Freeform surface re-parameterization, Ricci Flow, G1 continuous on NURBS surfaces</li>
<li><strong>Computer Graphics and Data Visualization:</strong> Multi-resolution methods, Forensic data analysis</li>
<li><strong>Data Mining and Data Analysis:</strong> Frequent pattern mining</li>
</ul>


<h2 id="education">EDUCATION</h2>


<p><strong>B.E.</strong> in <strong>Software Engineering</strong> &nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; 09/2010-06/2014(expected) <br />
Shandong University, Jinan, China <br />
Average: 89.27 (Total,top 7%), 90.78(Major) <br />
GPA: 3.74(Total), 3.8(Major)<br />
<a href="https://www.dropbox.com/s/jejti1bxpb8y3xx/course_profile_chenjianfeng.pdf">Course Profile</a></p>

<h2 id="project">PROJECT LIST</h2>




<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="http://chenjianfeng.net/images/equiareal.jpeg" style="width:200px;height:200px;"/></td><td><p align=left>  <b>Equiareal parameterizations of NURBS surfaces</b><br /> Advisor: Prof.<a href="http://vr.sdu.edu.cn/~yyj">Yijun Yang</a> | 2012-08 to 2013-04<br \>In this project, we studied the differential geometry of NURBS surfaces, optimized the equiareality of given NURBS surfaces using Mobius transformations. More specifically, I provided an explicit solution for Bezier/ B-spline surfaces and numerical solutions for NURBS to render the coefficients of the Mobius transformations. Finally, we gave some examples to show the performance of our algorithm.</p></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><img src="http://chenjianfeng.net/images/generalN.jpeg" style="width:200px;height:200px;"/></td><td><p align=left> <b>General rational bilinear transformation of NURBS surfaces</b><br /> Advisor: Prof. <a href="http://vr.sdu.edu.cn/~yyj">Yijun Yang</a> | 2013-04 to current <br \>In the project, we try to improve the conformity of NURBS surfaces by an optimization algorithm using general bilinear transformations. Now we are verifying the correctness and the practicability of the algorithm. Finally we will develop some example to show the performance of the algorithm.</p></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><img src="http://chenjianfeng.net/images/innotraffic.jpeg" style="width:200px;height:200px;"/></td><td><p align=left><b>InnoTraffic-Intelligent navigation system</b> <br \> Advisor: Prof. Hongjun Dai | 2012-09 to 2012-12
<br \> In this system, we first developed a model to express various kinds of roads, overpass or tunnel etc. in the city. Then we analyzed the real-time data collected from the system by the cellular automation model. In addition, we also developed an android app based on this system. The app won the Second Prize in International Contest of Applications in Network of Things (China) 2013.</p></td>
</tr>
<td><img src="http://chenjianfeng.net/images/hadoop.jpeg" style="width:200px;height:200px;"/></td><td> <p align = left><b>Electronic trading system with Hadoop storage</b><br />Advisor: Prof. Lizhen Cui | 2012-03 to 2012-07<br \>In this project, I studied the widely used distributed storage system-Hadoop and revised the “map” algorithm in original Hadoop system so that it can be suitable for the electronic trading use. In addition to this, we also developed a demo of electronic trading system whose storage system is our revised Hadoop system.</p></td>
</tr>

<td><img src="http://chenjianfeng.net/images/humming.jpeg" style="width:200px;height:200px;"/></td><td><p align = left> <b>Music information retrieval system via humming</b><br /> Advisor: Prof. Hongjun Dai | 2012-12 to 2013-02<br />In this interesting project, we tried to develop a music information retrieval system. We developed a model to “describe” the characteristic of the song. When the humming sound collected by an android app, we calculated the main characteristic of the sound and matched it from our database.</p></td>
</tr>
<td><img src="http://chenjianfeng.net/images/kmeans.GIF" style="width:200px;height:200px;"/></td><td><p align = left> <b>An improved k-means clustering algorithm and its application</b><br \>Advisor: Prof. Lizhen Cui | 2013-04 to 2013-10<br \>Clustering plays an increasingly important role in data mining and data analysis. We illustrated an improved clustering algorithm- K-means Algorithm, which can be accomplished much more easily and faster than many other similar algorithm.</p></td>
</tr>
<td><img src="http://chenjianfeng.net/images/cuda.GIF" style="width:200px;height:100px;"/></td><td><p align = left> <b>Research on parallel computing platform-CUDA</b><br \>Advisor: Prof. Weiguo Lui | 2012-08 to 2013-03 <br \>GPU-accelerated computing is one high theme in computer science world nowadays. Pioneered in 2007 by NVIDIA, CUDA has become a widely used tool. In this project, I just tried to learn the base CUDA programming and developed some code in order to compare CPU computing from GPU computing.<p></td>
</tr>
<td><img src="http://chenjianfeng.net/images/btree.GIF" style="width:200px;height:200px;"/></td><td><p align = left><b>Research on the query and update efficiency of B-Tree structure</b><br \>This is my course design of Data Structure class. To begin this course design, I first studied the structure of B-Tree and the common operation upon it. Then I wrote a B-Tree using C++, analyzed the spatial complexity and time complexity of the B-Tree and its operation. Finally, I also compared this data structure with other similar data structure-B* Tree, B+ Tree<p></td>
</tr>
<td><img src="http://chenjianfeng.net/images/PL01.GIF" style="width:200px;height:150px;"/></td><td><p align = left><b>The compiler for PL0/1 Language</b><br \>Adviser: Prof. Hongze Qiu | 2012-10 to 2013-01<br \>PL0/1 is an artificial simple computer language. I have finished a simple complier which can validates the program, converts it to Assembly-like language and execute it. The compiler could be divided into several parts: lexical analyzer, syntactic analyzer, pseudo code generator, etc.</p></td>
</tr>
<td><img src="http://chenjianfeng.net/images/generalN.jpeg" style="width:120px;height:120px;"/></td><td>A smart camera with cloud storage for android</td>
</tr>
<td><img src="http://chenjianfeng.net/images/generalN.jpeg" style="width:120px;height:120px;"/></td><td>Digital system experiment</td>
</tr>
</table>




<h2 id="pu">PUBLICATIONS AND DISSERTIONS</h2>


<ul>
<li><h4>Equiareal parameterizations of NURBS surfaces</h4>

<p><strong>Sci- Graphic Models, accepted, 2013</strong> [<a href="https://docs.google.com/file/d/0ByLC3dVEBaE_UWJ0QVJqWjlRWTQ/edit?usp=sharin">pdf</a>]<br \>
The equiareality of freeform surfaces greatly affects the results of visualization and tessellation applications, especially when dealing with extruding and intruding shapes. To improve the equiareality of given freeform surfaces, we present an optimization algorithm using the Mobius transformations in the paper.</p></li>
<li><h4>An Interest-based Social Networking Content Recommendation Method</h4>

<p><strong>CSCD- Journal of Mathematics in Practice and Theory, accepted ,2013</strong> [<a href="">pdf-Chinese</a>] <br \>
Effective content recommendation provide users with convenient and accurate access to contents of their interest, which is a significant approach to develop social network. This paper represents an interest-based Recommendation method (IRM) relating to social network. It collects user interest in order to build a user-interest-content model then presents an interest-based content recommendation sequence algorithm and verifies it.</p></li>
<li><h4>Optimizing conformity of NURBS surfaces using general bilinear transformations</h4>

<p><strong>Writing now</strong><br \>
The conformity of NURBS surfaces greatly affects rendering and tessellation results. To improve the conformity of NURBS surfaces, an optimization algorithm using general bilinear transformations is presented in this paper. This paper was inspired by the first paper (Equiareal parameterizations of NURBS surfaces), and we use a more general bilinear transformations to re-parameterize the surfaces, rather than merely use the limited Mobius transformations.</p></li>
<li><h4>Intelligent Navigation System basing Data Mining and Real-time Traffic</h4>

<p><strong>Paper won the first prize for the science creation competition, Shandong University, 2012</strong> <br \>
Without taking the real-time traffic situation into consideration, the typical navigation system merely receive the system users&#8217; requirement and return them a shortest path, which is obviously limited. In this paper, we represent a totally model to build a much more effective navigation system. This model begins with collect the real-time traffic situation from four-dimensional source, analyzes the traffic data by a cellular automata, and then generate an optimal path to the user. This paper is one of the interim results for the university innovation project.</p></li>
</ul>


<h2 id="ce">CERTIFICATIONS</h2>


<ul>
<li>IBM DB2 Academic Certificate</li>
<li>IBM XML Certificate</li>
<li>IBM Websphere Certificate</li>
<li>Software College training center (SDU) Certificate</li>
</ul>


<h2 id="me">MEMBERSHIP</h2>


<ul>
<li>Student Union</li>
<li><a href="http://www.bchine.com/">Bchine</a> Student Innovation Lab</li>
<li>Research Center of Human-Computer Interaction &amp; Virtual Reality[<a href="http://vr.sdu.edu.cn">link(Chinese)</a>]</li>
<li>Cycling Association of Shandong University (CASDU)</li>
<li>Mathematical Modeling Club of Shandong University</li>
<li>Robot Fish Interest Group</li>
</ul>


<h2 id="tr">TRAVEL EXPERIENCE</h2>



]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
